Goin' out tonight, changes into something red
Her mother doesn't like that kind of dress
Everything she never had, she's showing up
Driving too fast, Moon is breaking through her ear
She said if something that she won't forget
Haven't no regrets, it's all that she really wants
Only getting on the baby
And I've been thinking about Leyla
Does it ever drive you crazy?
Just how fast the night
Chained us everything that you've ever dreamed of
Is superior in when you wake up
What there's nothing to be afraid of
Even when I change us, it will never change me
Just in the night, doubts are running around her head
He's bleeding, hearts behind a cigarette
Hot as big a loud and she doesn't want it to start
Moving too fast, Moon is lighting up a skin
She's falling, doesn't even know we yet
Haven't no regrets, it's all that she really wants
Only getting on the baby
And I've been thinking about Leyla
Does it ever drive you crazy?
Just how fast the night changes
Everything you've ever dreamed of
Disappearing when you wake up
What there's nothing to be afraid of
Even when I change us, it will never change me and you
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Though we're now tonight, changes into something res
Her mother does it like that kind of
Trans reminder of the missing piece of innocent she loves
Only getting on the baby
Nothing thinking about Leyla
Does it ever drive you crazy?
Just how fast the night changes
Everything you've ever dreamed of
Disappearing when you wake up
What there's nothing to be afraid of
Even when I change us, everything you've ever dreamed of
Disappearing when you wake up
What there's nothing to be afraid of
Even when I change us, it will never change
Baby, you'll never change baby
You'll never change me and you